http://www.crippenlandru.com/shop/oscommerce-2.3.4/catalog/privacy.php?osCsid=5fc3b3f63ffb32df4237612be270f250

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Top » Catalog » Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Information Security
Crippen & Landru has our own SSL to protect your personal information. Secure servers guarantee that information passed from one party to another via that server cannot be intercepted by any third party. To view our secure certification details click the Blue Host logo below.
If you experience any difficulties connecting to the secure site, please contact us at webmaster@crippenlandru.com with a detailed explanation of your problem.
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for www.crippenlandru.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
• See what data we have about you, if any.
• Change/correct any data we have about you.
• Have us delete any data we have about you.
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 877-622-6656 or via email.
Continue
Categories Current Booklist (124)Lost Classics (43)Out of Print (40)Non-Fiction (2)Upcoming Releases Upcoming Releases eBook Availabilty
Cover Artists Please SelectBarbara Mitchel..Carol HeyerChristina Lubos..Deborah MillerErin WellsGail CrossGwen MandleyJackie WebberJeff WongJuha LindroosLinda WeatherlyLuke Williams B..Melanie FalkTom RobertsVictoria Russel..
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
What's New? Hunt in the Dark and Other Fatal Pursuits$0.00
Information
Shipping & Returns Privacy Notice Join Our Newsletter About Us Discounts and Subscriptions Gift Voucher FAQ Trivia and Nooses Links Contact Us
We Accept
Shopping Cart0 items
Bestsellers Challenge The ImpossibleAll But ImpossibleThe Man Who Read MysteriesHoch's LadiesThe Zanzibar Shirt and Other StoriesThe Cases of Lieutenant Timothy TrantThe Puzzles of Peter DuluthFuneral in the FogMy Mother, The Detective: The Complete "Mom" Short Stories Enlarged editionHot Cash, Cold Clews
Reviews When I was younger in the 60s and 70s I read everything Mr.
..
Crippen & Landru Publishers
P.O. Box 532057  ·  Cincinnati, OH 45253
·  Phone (Toll Free) 844-622-6656
Questions or comments? Please email webmaster@crippenlandru.com<
Copyright © 2020 Crippen & LandruPowered by osCommerce
